Come to the night, the cards laid out for show
Star shine is so bright, watch the secret sun fall
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what
card an open door feel the romance in every arcane lore
Wow, guys. Hold on a second. Yeah. I didn't end that. Hold on. Let's see what's going on here.
Hey, Jamie. Yeah, I don't know. Everyone seems like they're mad or something like that, but
I think it's just kind of funny. It's like, I don't need, I'm not like such a control freak. I
need to have control 24. No, it's whatever. You know, I can read reliquish control for like a little
Yeah, I have a that I hope goes comes back if not then I'll wrap it up around one
I'll give him some time soon. It's I don't know. It's gonna get a little exhausting. I do have to try to
Try to get a little bit of rest, but
No, everyone's good tonight. Oh, yeah, and I and spunky didn't come back as I have these cards that she got me
But I did promise her I read her first from them and so I'm gonna wait for her to get here to show them
but they're really cool true crime cards and
Yeah, very cool
which I cannot wait to read from,
but I'm gonna wait for her.
I'm gonna wait for her first.
Ah, so how's everybody doing tonight?
It looks a little bit quiet.
Maybe people are tired of the show's ending
and starting up again, but I don't know.
There's some stuff that maybe I just know
when's the right time to end the panel.
It's certain, I just don't want shows to, you know,
get banned and stuff.
So hopefully you guys understand.
I am sorry ghost and it goes to doing another 10 bucks right at the end of that panel there. So
you know, he's
Extremely generous and I hey Nick. How are you game over? Maybe it is
But
Yeah
Okay, if Ghost doesn't get here in 9 minutes, I'm going to end the panel for the night.
I do have some more cards.
Let me see.
Do I have more cards to show anybody?
I don't know if I have more cards.
Do I have more cards?
Let me see.
you've seen all of them. I'm actually restarted the Tarot series. I mean that was that other one
was a kind of a run through. I'm working with the very powerful AI. Okay. I'm gonna wait a few
minutes more and it looks like people might not be coming back. If they don't, it's okay.
Pull you a car sure
In the chain
I'm gonna put Jamie from the alien deck today anyone want some cards tonight. I got everything for you. Okay. Oh
Okay, we have we have the death card is that gaudy there's kind of looks like gaudy right there
You have the death card Jamie that made that it means something in the past has been put to rest, you know and
You know, I know you've been through some serious stuff lately
And I don't think it has anything to do with the actual physical death. I think it has to do with
Something that's actually not dead because you see death right there is not quite dead, right? That is alive, right? And so
Okay, so maybe they're into something.
Then we have the, okay, we have the three of cups.
Three of cups, that is like a celebrating with people.
You know, this is a, you're having a,
opening a bottle up with your friends
and having a good time,
but maybe there's one that likes more than the other.
You never know every dynamic happening in the relationship
because there's other people involved, right?
We all we know is ourselves, right?
So you might be dealing with that.
Okay, this is the six of swords. So six. Okay. So this is like a six of swords is going to be like a, like a lot of worrying about something like you're not being able to, to quite, you know, rest, because you're worried about something, but I'd say, you know, don't worry too much, things will work out. I have some advice for you to Jamie.
The advice is seven of cups the advice is to examine all your options really carefully like look like look
There's gonna be like many options for you. Okay, and some are gonna be better than the others. They're all gonna be
Maybe appealing and visually right and so you have to
Decide which one you want the most. Oh
Okay, I care Nick. I like to do is ask I was gonna re-mod you it's just like I forget okay, so I'll re-mod you you don't have to like
Talk about me like in the third person like right here
Okay
Yeah, because Nick is you're fine Modnik I'm not mad at you Nick I like I'm just I'm just an asshole sometimes right?
It's like like I was you know sometimes like last night maybe but it's not don't mean it
Just can't
Okay, so here Nick
Who then I insanity goes hijacks the piano. Okay, here we go
In a friendly way. Okay, it's a joke hilarity and suit. Okay, so Nick
Okay, now you can post your link, okay?
Okay, well five more minutes we got five minutes left and
Your ghost is gonna come run the panel tonight or I'm gonna be ending it at one and it was the kind of
A little bit of a wild night tonight, you know, I mean guys, I will be doing at least one day a week. I'll be doing
Like a free open panel, I'll just do a open panel show, you know at least one day a week, but you know
That's about all I want to I want to have the pan so it's not it's monetized unless it's a
You know sponsors, but I think spot the sponsorships great for people
for creators and anybody that has anything to promote if you have any kind of business like to promote either to or
You know or you have a friend that has business to promote you can put the friends
I mean it's like so it is and I think it is quality advertising
You know I do we do have great people on the show that are interested in checking out people who've deleted with the show, okay?
so
Yep, okay, so
How are we doing guys that we have a countdown now we have a it's a 1256 we have four minutes if by by 1 a.m
No one comes
I'm out of here tonight. It seems like it seems that maybe people are a little bit a little bit moody and
You know the best night for it, and I'm sorry. I know people are people are getting mad at me
Fine give
I don't know. I think I really have to go
But I mean I might be back at like two in the morning. Hey, she's an issue now
Yeah, I'm a little traumatized
I saw Vicky's boobs and she was like playing with them on like on a camera for at least over a minute
they were
Enormous like I'm never like first. I mean this
I was looking at a mountain or I just don't they were
Disturbing
And I've seen flirty diamonds boobs, you know, it's like so I've you know, I'm just saying you know
You've never seen anything like this. You've never seen anything like this
shocking
Almost almost not real almost almost like unbelievable
So I'm a little bit shaken up right now. You know who Vicky is. She's always so nice
She's always like smiling a little pleasant smile. Mm-hmm, and she was laughing. She was she was laughing hysterically
So I think she must be like a queen like it's kind of troll Queen or something like that
I don't thank you for not coming on panel and doing that that would have been
No, the tickle through me, but I don't know I don't I just
Need to go wash my eyes out with the soap
It's okay big yeah, I'm just I'm just playing with it. I mean yeah, they were not was it was kind of shocking
I mean you can't believe you did that. I can't really believe you wanted me to see that
Well, why would you want me to see that? I'm a gay guy
So you know, I wouldn't yeah, I wouldn't be perverted about it
Well
We have key no potato head they look like they looked like
Mr. Mrs. Potato had exploded on her chest. I mean basically like that. I mean or like I don't even there's a mr. Mrs.
Mashed potato. I don't know it was I don't know what I was looking at
I thought I was looking at some him underwater being for a minute and then I
Thought the human features and I was like, oh, I know her
Yeah guys, okay, so ghost took off. I got I did give ghost my phone number
And so if he got my phone number, he should be able to call me
Ball in a sock. Yeah, so
Hey, this is me money. I made somebody. Yep, and I think we'll be we'll be in a better mood tomorrow
Everyone will be it'll be calm down a little bit ghost can call me back because I gave my number back stage
You can't say I didn't try to tell you where to get a hold of me tonight. Okay, but I guess you are
On some of the panel maybe or
But I love you ghosts and I thank you so much
It is 1 a.m. I'm gonna be I might be back in them
You know, maybe a couple hours or something. We'll see how I feel. Okay, but I love you guys. See you soon